

ROMJAN

009-715-278070

romjanbepari727@gmail.com

Dubai United Arab Emirates

WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- https://romjan123.github.i o/romjan/
- https://twitter.com /romjan1995
- https://linkedin.com /in/romjan1995

SKILLS

- Decision-Making
- Flexible and Adaptable
- · Active Listening
- Excellent Communication
- Analytical and Critical Thinking
- Interpersonal Communication
- Organization and Time Management

LANGUAGES

Arabic

Elementary (A2)

English

Upper intermediate (B2)

Hindi

Advanced (C1)

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Goal-focused Accountant with record of accurate reporting and budget management. Offering 2 years of experience handling finances for 5 locations. Processed payroll, budgets, reports, audits, journals, expenditures and payments. Diligently maintains latest training on tax regulations and legal issues impacting financial operations.

WORK HISTORY

February 2021 - Current

Assistant Accountant, Ayesha Ismaeil Technical Services, Dubai, AE

- Reviewed general ledger entries and assessed accuracy.
- Monitored status of accounts receivable and payable to facilitate prompt processing.
- Communicated with suppliers to reconcile invoice payments.
- Reconciled company accounts for credit cards, employee expenses and commissions.
- Balanced reports to submit for approval and verification.
- Set up and improved accounting systems and processes to meet business needs and maximize operational success.
- Evaluated and improved accuracy and completeness of financial records.
- Maintained accurate and complete documentation for financial department procedures to facilitate new employee training.

July 2017 - July 2019

Sales Merchandiser, Arabian Trading Supplyer, Riyadh, SA

- Advanced sales cycle plans by maximizing placement of promotions, point of sale materials and product visibility.
- Planned and coordinated product availability for advertising and promotion purposes.
- Ran markdown reports, managed store replenishment and analyzed buying reports.
- Removed damaged, out-of-code, not-in-set and discontinued items from displays.
- Updated pricing and signage to complete product displays and educate customers.
- Answered customer questions regarding store merchandise, department information and pricing.
- Inspected merchandise for quality and arranged proper display location on floor.
- Verified products appeared at correct locations in proper quantities.
- Monitored inventory levels and kept adequate stock in product displays on sales floor.
- Oversaw procurement of products and apparel for CBD retail chain store, monitoring annual budget of \$170000

EDUCATION

January 2019

Under Graduate, Accounting And Business Management

National University Of Bangladesh, Dhaka

- Professional development completed in Accounting
- Completed BBA Honors 2 Semester Out of 4 Semester

August 2015

High School Diploma

Porbo Madaripur College, Dhaka

CERTIFICATIONS

• Certified Accountant Assistant, Ayesha Ismaeil Technical Services - 2021-2022